# Imron Hajiahmad

Logistics Coordinator / Instructor

### Contact

**Address** 

Mountain View, CA, 94040

**Phone** 

(916) 764-4580

E-mail

imronha@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/imronha/

**WWW** 

www.imronha.com

## **Skills**

Coordinating logistics

Communication

Time Management

Teamwork

Self-Motivation

HTML

CSS

Javascript

Python

MERN Stack

**MEAN Stack** 

Git/Github

Swift

Experienced logistics coordinator professional with a wide range of skills and interests ranging from software development, teaching, coaching, and management. A team player with an efficiency-driven, organized, and resilient mindset that values integrity and always strives to ensure customer satisfaction and overall excellence with company goals in mind.

# **Work History**

#### 2018 -Current

## **Logistics Coordinator / Instructor**

S.A.M. Singapore Math, Millbrae, CA

- Actively improved nearly 100% of student's math test scores within months of attendance by using Singapore Mathematics to instill confidence and conceptual understanding of core topics.
- Implemented new processes and procedures to improve instructor grading time, accuracy, teaching methodology, and communication between instructors, students, and parents.
- Created custom python scripts to automate certain processes and procedures to increase instructor efficiency by over 50%.

#### 2018 - 2019

# Coding Instructor

KidzToPros LLC, San Jose, CA

 Improved teaching methodology to effectively teach large classrooms of 30 students to ignite interest and curiosity in coding and science.

#### 2017 - 2018

## IT and Systems Administrator 2017-2018

Samirian Chemicals Inc., Campbell, CA

 Created, tested and implemented new scripts for NetSuite to help automate tasks and increase efficiency for sales, marketing, and current vendors. Updated currently deployed scripts from SuiteScript 1.0 to SuiteScript 2.0 to increase code reusability and readability.

#### 2013 - 2017

#### **Dietetic Assistant**

UC Davis Medical Center, Sacramento, CA

- Helped increase patient satisfaction by 20% through prioritizing patient health, safety, and satisfaction by meticulously and accurately processing patient care orders.
- Provided input on current and past department policies in order to improve departmental productivity, patient safety, patient satisfaction, and overall hospital performance despite increasing patient population.
- Ensured that patient meal preferences adhere to dietary restrictions by contacting individuals to discuss

Flutter/Dart

# Languages

English

Japanese

Cham

Arabic

- current therapeutic prescriptions, allergies, and fluid restrictions with nearly 100% accuracy.
- Efficiently prioritized time sensitive orders (such as baby formulas, enteral tube feedings, dietary restrictions etc.) in order to provide 100% completion rate of time sensitive material while simultaneously receiving high volumes of phone calls from nurses, doctors, hosts, and other hospital staff.

## **Education**

2017-06 -2017-09 Coding Bootcamp Graduate: Software

**Engineering** 

Coding Dojo - San Jose

2008 - 2012

Bachelor of Science: Clinical Nutrition, Japanese

University of California - Davis - Davis, CA Member of the UC Davis Men's Volleyball Club Team

## **Interests**

Coding Frameworks

STEM Blogs, videos, documentaries

Puzzles and Games

Volleyball (Indoor and outdoor)

Traveling

Photography

Videography

Science / Physics / Astronomy, etc

Hiking, Swimming, and other outdoor activities